<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<products>
  <product>
    <aisle>Meat</aisle>
    <name>Axolotl</name>
    <author>Matthew Kazemie ID: 40190450</author>
    <image>img/Axlot.png</image>
    <important_details/>
    <extra_details>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>Taste: Tastes like freshwater fish</p>
        <p>1 Axolotl Mass: 300gr</p>
        <p>1 Axolotl Carbohyrate: 0gr</p>
        <br />
        <p>
          By 2020 <strong>Anno Domini</strong>, these creatures were
          considered critically endangered but thanks to cloning technology
          created by<mark>DO NOT READ THIS</mark> in the earth year<mark
            >THIS YEAR HAS MANY DIGITS</mark
          >, we can now deliver to you the experience of Axolotl. Anybody
          with an interest in ancient human cuisine will be very happy
          preparing their own Axolotl.
        </p>
        <p>
          These creatures have talents that include regenerating body parts
          and being inbred.
        </p>
       ]]>
    </extra_details>
    <types>
      <type>
        <typeID>normal-axolotl</typeID>
        <tname>Normal Axolotl</tname>
        <multiplier>1</multiplier>
      </type>
      <type>
        <typeID>super-axolotl</typeID>
        <tname>Genetically Modified Super-Axolotl</tname>
        <multiplier>2</multiplier>
      </type>
    </types>
    <price>10000</price>
    <price_text>Price: $10000 99% off</price_text>
    <adjusted_price>100</adjusted_price>
  </product>
  <product>
    <aisle>Meat</aisle>
    <name>Meat Computer</name>
    <author>Matthew Kazemie ID: 40190450</author>
    <image>img/MeatModelX.png</image>
    <important_details>
      <![CDATA[
      <h4>Do not consume if human</h4>
          <h5>Consumption if human may cause:</h5>
          <li>
            <ul>
              <h5>Ataxia</h5>
            </ul>
            <ul>
              <h5>Dysphagia</h5>
            </ul>
            <ul>
              <h5>Brain Theft</h5>
            </ul>
          </li>
       ]]>
    </important_details>
    <extra_details>
      <![CDATA[
      <div id="not-schizophrenia" style="display: block">
        <p>Taste: Tastes like human brain</p>
        <p>1 MEAT Computer Mass: 3000gr</p>
        <p>1 MEAT Computer Carbohyrate: 0gr</p>
        <p>Is Biodegradable</p>
        <br />
        <p>
          Some people would mistakenly call the times we live in grim or
          dark but clearly, today is a time of prosperity like no other.
          Nothing shows this fact off like the latest model of the MEAT
          Computer.
          <br />
          The MEAT Model X can achieve a calculation speed of 10 PFLOPS at
          very little energy cost. Traditional computers would take the
          amount of energy required to power a Capital LightRacer starship
          for an hour if they were to try and match what a MEAT Model X
          can do in a day. Evolution has built a better computer than
          engineers ever could.
        </p>
        <br />
        <p>
          You are entitled to exchange your purchased Meat Computer for a
          brand new one if you experience:
        </p>
        <li>
          <ul>
            Attempts at communication
          </ul>
          <ul>
            Strange Noises
          </ul>
          <ul>
            Unexpected Shutdowns
          </ul>
        </li>
        <h5>Disclaimer:</h5>
        <h5>
          From now on we will refrain from using brains from state
          provided prisoners and will solely use lab-grown brains.
        </h5>
        <h5>We are sorry for any distress we may have caused.</h5>
      </div>

      <button onclick="TogglePsychosis()">You are being fed lies</button>
      <div id="schizophrenia" style="display: none">
        <h1>Don't you think something is wrong here?</h1>
        <h3>You are being lied to.</h3>
        <h3>The information you were fed doesn't add up.</h3>
        <p>
          If humans no longer exist on Earth then how do we have human
          brains to compute with? Were humans exiled from Earth? These
          computers wouldn't be earth products then.
        </p>
        <h3>Aren't you human?</h3>
        <p>
          You are <mark>NOT</mark> experiencing psychosis. Time doesn't
          work the way you think it does.
        </p>
        <h2>Join the People's Revolution</h2>
        <h2>You have nothing to lose but your brain</h2>
      </div>
       ]]>
    </extra_details>
    <types>
      <type>
        <typeID>normal</typeID>
        <tname>Normal MEAT Model X</tname>
        <multiplier>1</multiplier>
      </type>
    </types>
    <price>100000</price>
    <price_text>Price: $100000 99% off</price_text>
    <adjusted_price>1000</adjusted_price>
  </product>
  <product>
    <aisle>Meat</aisle>
    <name>Harrier</name>
    <author>Matthew Kazemie ID: 40190450</author>
    <image>img/HarrierA.png</image>
    <important_details/>
    <extra_details>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>Taste: Feathers, Disgusting</p>
        <p>1 Harrier Mass: 400gr</p>
        <p>1 Harrier Carbohyrate: 0gr</p>
        <br />
        <p>
          An ancient bird with murderous tendencies. Trained to kill any pest that makes the mistake of passing by your home. 
          After you purchase your very own harrier, red will rain from the sky and the short lives of any pests or 
          babies will be savagely violent!
        </p>
       ]]>
    </extra_details>
    <types>
      <type>
        <typeID>normal-harrier</typeID>
        <tname>Normal Harrier</tname>
        <multiplier>1</multiplier>
      </type>
      <type>
        <typeID>combat-harrier</typeID>
        <tname>Combat Harrier</tname>
        <multiplier>16</multiplier>
      </type>
    </types>
    <price>20</price>
    <price_text>Price: $20</price_text>
    <adjusted_price>20</adjusted_price>
  </product>
  <product>
    <aisle>Clothing</aisle>
    <name>Jeans</name>
    <author>Boisghur Shishani ID: 40170574</author>
    <image>img/Jeans.jpg</image>
    <important_details/>
    <extra_details>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>
              Human believed that this item would grant them strength and
              protection in battle. The material is only 1mm (human measurement)
              thick however it is tough enough to protect against the primitive
              human weapons such as nuclear bombs and guns. Some humans would
              wear jeans that were ripped as a symbol of their strength and
              courage. This was done to prove that noone could defeat them in
              battle even with their obvious weakness.
            </p>
            <p>
              It is believed that the more rips you had in your jeans the more
              powerful and respected you were within your society. Our products
              do not come with rips, however you can easily add some rips at
              home by using your lightsaber.
            </p>
       ]]>
    </extra_details>
    <types>
      <type>
        <typeID>jeans</typeID>
        <tname>Jeans</tname>
        <multiplier>1</multiplier>
      </type>
    </types>
    <price>1000</price>
    <price_text>Price: $1000</price_text>
    <adjusted_price>1000</adjusted_price>
  </product>

<product>
    <aisle>Clothing</aisle>
    <name>Necktie</name>
    <author>Boisghur Shishani ID: 40170574</author>
    <image>img/Tie.jpg</image>
    <important_details/>
    <extra_details>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>
              The necktie was a thin piece of fabric which humans wore around
              their upper vertebrae. In cases of emergency they would use this
              fabric as a makeshift rope or even as a whip for self defense.
              Wearing a necktie was a symbol of a persons dominance and
              aggression for humans.
            </p>
            <p>
              The necktie was primarily worn by the male gender, the current
              theory on this is that it was originially used to hide the adam's
              apple which only appears in the males of the species.
            </p>
       ]]>
    </extra_details>
    <types>
      <type>
        <typeID>necktie</typeID>
        <tname>Necktie</tname>
        <multiplier>1</multiplier>
      </type>
    </types>
    <price>150</price>
    <price_text>Price: $150</price_text>
    <adjusted_price>150</adjusted_price>
  </product>

  <product>
    <aisle>Clothing</aisle>
    <name>Shoes</name>
    <author>Boisghur Shishani ID: 40170574</author>
    <image>img/Shoes.jpg</image>
    <important_details/>
    <extra_details>
      <![CDATA[
       <p>
              This product must be ordered in pairs where each shoe will be a mirror image of its pair. This is because of the strange form of human feet.
              Shoes were an important cultural aspect of humans around the world. Some humans, such as Michael Jordan, were named after shoes as the humans believed
               this would grant them special powers and abilities in athletic competitions. These shoes were made to protect human feet, however these can still be 
               used by tentacled species by simply placing your tentacles inside the shoe's hole and tightening and tying the straps attached. 
            </p>
            <p>
              During the Humans final century on earth creasing a pair of shoes was considered an act of terrorism and was punishable by life-time imprisonment. However, it is important to remember that the average human
               lifetime was only around 150 years.
            </p>
       ]]>
    </extra_details>
    <types>
      <type>
        <typeID>shoes</typeID>
        <tname>Shoes</tname>
        <multiplier>1</multiplier>
      </type>
    </types>
    <price>500</price>
    <price_text>Price: $500</price_text>
    <adjusted_price>500</adjusted_price>
  </product>

  <product>
    <aisle>Clothing</aisle>
    <name>T-shirt</name>
    <author>Boisghur Shishani ID: 40170574</author>
    <image>img/tShirt.jpg</image>
    <important_details/>
    <extra_details>
      <![CDATA[
       <p>
              Despite being a bipedal species, the humans wore this item with
              only one opening for both of their legs. This item was thought to
              be highly sought after during the humans rule over the planet
              Earth C-137. Many intergalactic species can still fit in this item
              thanks to the multiple holes. For all tripedal species and above,
              do not worry, This item will fit you as well provided you put the
              majority of your limbs through the largest hole in the bottom.
            </p>
            <p>
              The T-shirt was worn by all genders, however it is believed that
              this item was only available to the socioeconomic elites and
              therefore is a very valuable collectors item
            </p>
       ]]>
    </extra_details>
    <types>
      <type>
        <typeID>tshirt</typeID>
        <tname>T-shirt</tname>
        <multiplier>1</multiplier>
      </type>
    </types>
    <price>3000</price>
    <price_text>Price: $3000</price_text>
    <adjusted_price>3000</adjusted_price>
  </product>

  <product>
    <aisle>Clothing</aisle>
    <name>Skirt</name>
    <author>Boisghur Shishani ID: 40170574</author>
    <image>img/Skirt.jpg</image>
    <important_details/>
    <extra_details>
      <![CDATA[
       <p>
              Despite being a bipedal species, the humans wore this item with
              only one opening for both of their legs. This clothing greatly
              improved agility, which was useful for the species to evade
              predators when attacked. This item was one of the main reasons the
              human species survived for as long as they did despite their small
              size and low level of intellect.
            </p>
            <p>The skirt was worn primarily by the female gender.</p>
       ]]>
    </extra_details>
    <types>
      <type>
        <typeID>skirt</typeID>
        <tname>Skirt</tname>
        <multiplier>1</multiplier>
      </type>
    </types>
    <price>200</price>
    <price_text>Price: $200</price_text>
    <adjusted_price>200</adjusted_price>
  </product>

  <product>
    <aisle>Fruit</aisle>
    <name>Dragonfruit</name>
    <author>Pierre Chevalier ID: 40098342</author>
    <image>img/dragonfruit.png</image>
    <important_details/>
    <extra_details>
      <![CDATA[
       <p>
        <p>Taste: mildly sweet, refreshing</p>
		<p>1 Dragonfruit weighs from 200 g to 1 kg</p>
		<p>Carbohydrates in 1 average Dragonfruit: 50g</p>
		<br></br>
		<p>
			Humans developed an obsession with this fruit that is as of yet unexplained. Its taste has been
			described as "mild" and even "lame", but it has been rumored to have stamina enhancing abilities,
			and it doubtlessly has an appearance as cool as its name.
		</p>
       ]]>
    </extra_details>
    <types>
      <type>
        <typeID>dragonfruit</typeID>
        <tname>Dragonfruit</tname>
        <multiplier>1</multiplier>
      </type>
    </types>
    <price>200</price>
    <price_text>Price: $200</price_text>
    <adjusted_price>200</adjusted_price>
  </product>
</products>
